A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), SG 3, Series 14 FA1475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), 1925-2006; 14
  - IHP Audiovisual Materials, 10
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - Tape 3, 2003 October 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15236)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting - Tape 4, 2003 October 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15237)